positype.com 2019-08-08

# Privacy Policy ← Positype

By using this website, you agree to our privacy policy terms as outlined below. If you do not agree to these terms, do not access or use this site. Positype reserves the right to change these terms at any time. Your use of this site will be subject to the most current terms outlined here.

 **Your Personal Information.** We do not collect personal information on this site unless you choose to give it to us. The one place on the site where you can choose to give us personal information is by purchasing a typeface license, wherein we will ask you that you provide sufficient information to process this transaction, including: your name, address, phone number, email address, and (if a purchase is made) your credit card details. We do not collect identifiable information about you if you only browse our website.

 **How Your Personal Information Is Utilized.** We collect and retain only the information you choose to give to us and only in order to support your participation in the activities you select on this website. If you order a product that is to be electronically downloaded, the information is used to verify your credit card details, assign a valid license to use acquire fonts, deliver those items electronically, and to maintain your order history.

 **Securing Your Personal Information.** Access by you to your personal information is available through a password and unique customer ID (your email address) that you provide. We protect your credit card information at the time of purchase using SSL and other data encryption methods required for PCI compliance which have been developed to prevent unauthorized parties from intercepting such transmissions. Credit card data is held only during the transaction process and is not stored permanently on our secure server.

 **Maintaining Your Personal Information.** We are happy to provide you with access to any personal information that we hold about you. If it is wrong, please ask us to correct it. To ask for access and correction, see our contact details. You can ask to be removed from our mailing list at any time. Information provided will be stored by Positype only.
